Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Video Recordings, 1993-2005
  - Steinhardt Department of Music "Piano Inter-Studio", 19 Nov 2007; cuid1127; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - All University Sing, 9 Dec 1997; cuid1128; 2 videocassettes (Box 95)
  - The NYU Festival String Orchestra, 11 Mar 1998; cuid1129; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 71)
  - Yale Storm and Hot Pastrami, 4 Nov 1998; cuid1130; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 71)
  - Education Policy Breakfast "Black and White Acheivement", Unknown; cuid1131; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Does Money Matter?", 22 Mar 2001; cuid1132; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Closing the Achievement Gap", 13 Dec 2001; cuid1133; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "An Instructional Vision", 12 Dec 2001; cuid1134; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "The Purpose of Education", 25 Mar 2002; cuid1135; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Mathematics: Clear or Fuzzy?", 29 Apr 2003; cuid1136; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Gender Implications", 5 Apr 2000; cuid1137; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 95)
  - Installation of the 15th President, 26 Sep 2002; cuid1138; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 95)
  - Bobst Library, 28 Apr 1998; cuid1139; 2 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 71)
  - President Oliva Promotes New York University TV, 8 Aug 1995; cuid1140; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 71)
  - Hang Blix: Disarming Iraq, 15 Mar 2004; cuid1141; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - "Critical Topics in Food" Fales Series, 17 May 2005; cuid1142; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71, Box 95)
  - A Lecture with Helen Zia "Colliding into 2020", 5 October 2004; cuid1143; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Amy Goodman, 24 Feb 2004; cuid1144; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture in Philiosophy Noam Chomsky, 15 Nov 2004; cuid1145; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Bobst Library Anniversary, 16 Dec 2002; cuid1146; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 95)
  - Susana Baca, 15 July 2003; cuid1147; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy Peter Singer, 17 Nov 2003; cuid1148; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - MIAP Speakers Series: Dan Streible, 19 Nov 2004; cuid1149; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Fales Library Series: Marvin Taylor, 12 Feb 2003; cuid1150; 2 minidvs (Box 71, Box 95)
  - Hugh Masereld and Harry Belefonte in Conversation, 22 Feb 2005; cuid1151; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Scholars and Artists Episode 1, 20 Jan 2005; cuid1152; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - David Wojnarowicz and Peter Hujar, 20 Sep 2005; cuid1153; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - John Kerry Lecture, 20 Sep 2004; cuid1154; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Wagner School, 11 Oct 2000; cuid1155; 1 minidvs (Box 95)
  - Charlie Rose Lecture, 21 Nov 2003; cuid1156; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Jay Oliva Portrait Unveiling, 5 May 2003; cuid1157; 1 minidvs (Box 95)
  - Fales Lecture Series "Up is up, But So Is Down", 26 Oct 2006; cuid1158; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Robert Preston Tisch Dinner, 26 Jan 2006; cuid1159; 1 videocassettes (Box 71)
  - Skirball Center Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2 Oct 2003; cuid1160; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Skirball Center Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2 Oct 2003; cuid1161; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - TV 37 Clone Music, undated; cuid1162; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Kimmel Exterior Station ID, undated; cuid1163; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Kimmel Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 11 Jun 2003; cuid1164; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 71)
  - Puck Building Dedication and Debate, 23 Sep 2004; cuid1165; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - Hannah Kohn Tabacco Use Lecture, 30 Oct 2001; cuid1166; 1 minidvs (Box 71)
  - SS Proleterka Reading by Feur Jaeggy, 9 Dec 2003; cuid1167; 2 minidvs (Box 71)
  - America and Islam in a Global World, 24 Jan 2002; cuid1168; 5 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 72)
  - America and Islam in a Global World, 24 Jan 2002; cuid1169; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 72)
  - Domestic and Family Violence in the 21st Century, 2 Feb 2001; cuid1170; 6 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 72)
  - Carol Gilligan "Understanding Gender", 5 Apr 2000; cuid1171; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 72)
  - NYU Development Dr. Epstein Surgery, 26 Oct 1995; cuid1172; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 72)
  - Harold Levy Lecture, 26 Apr 2000; cuid1173; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 72)
  - John Lang and Todd Gitlin, 1 Dec 1998; cuid1174; 4 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - Spike Lee Black Genuis, 8 Oct 1998; cuid1175; 2 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - Downtown Poetry Reading at Fales Library, 27 Oct 1998; cuid1176; 1 videocassettes (Box 73)
  - African American Trade Unions at Bobst Library, 10 Feb 2000; cuid1177; 2 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - Dennis Cooper Panel, 2 Mar 2000; cuid1178; 2 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - New York University TV Alumni Interview Brian Frazee, 26 Aug 1998; cuid1179; 7 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 80)
  - NYU Celebrates Africana Studies, 25 Sep 1998; cuid1180; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - Carol Gilligan "Understanding Gender", 2 Apr 2000; cuid1181; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 73)
  - MCTP: Seminar Norm Fruchter, 30 Apr 2003; cuid1182; 2 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Women's Rights Conference, undated; cuid1183; 2 videocassettes (minidv) (Box 74)
  - "From Fundemental Principles to Selection Criteria" Barbara Goldsmith Preservation Lecture Series, Hal Erickson, 24 Jun 2002; cuid1184; 2 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Jack Schwartz Retirement Dinner, 29 Oct 2004; cuid1185; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Securing America in the 21st Century, 9 Sep 2005; cuid1186; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Courant Institute Interviews, 6 Oct 2005; cuid1187; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - The End of Poverty, Jeffrey Sachs, 5 Oct 2005; cuid1188; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Critical Topics in Food: Luxury Dining, 20 Oct 2005; cuid1189; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Gertrude Belle Elion, 11 Oct 2005; cuid1190; 2 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Jenny Holzer "For the City", undated; cuid1191; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Kimmel Opening Ceremony, 11 Jun 2003; cuid1192; 1 videocassettes (betacam) (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies Alumni Panel, 14 May 2005; cuid1193; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Amy Goodman Lecture, 1 Sep 2005; cuid1194; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Critical Topics in Food: Food Writers of Greenwich Village, 10 Mar 2006; cuid1195; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Culture and Communications, 1 Sep 2005; cuid1196; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Visions of a Changing Theater, undated; cuid1197; 5 minidvs (Box 74, Box 75)
  - The Moving Edge: The Place of Downtown Art in NYC, undated; cuid1198; 10 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74, Box 75)
  - The Moving Edge: The Place of Downtown Art in NYC, undated; cuid1199; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Simon Reynolds: Raw Footage, undated; cuid1200; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Downtown Show: Nightclubbing, n.d.; cuid1201; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - APA studies: Globalization and China Economic, 1 Sep 2006; cuid1202; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Neil Postman Symposium, undated; cuid1203; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - NYU Metro Regional Alumni Brooklyn Dodgers 1955, 15 Nov 2005; cuid1204; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Board of Trustees Dinner, 10 Apr 2005; cuid1205; 1 videocassettes (Box 74)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy, 16 Nov 2005; cuid1206; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - The Reality Show, 24 Oct 2005; cuid1207; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - The National Conference for Community and Justice, 9 Feb 2006; cuid1208; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - MIAP The Moving Image: Texts as Iodes of Metadata, 28 Oct 2005; cuid1209; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Convocation in Honor of Gordon Brown and Alan, 14 Dec 2005; cuid1210; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Taking Journalism Seriously, 21 Apr 2006; cuid1211; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Dean's Day, 13 May 2006; cuid1212; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - NYC TVC Reel, undated; cuid1213; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Image of Ben Franklin As Seen by Himself, 3 Feb 2006; cuid1214; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Image of Ben Franklin As Seen by Himself, 3 Feb 2006; cuid1215; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - The Reality Show 2005, cuid1216; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Stern Panel Dicussion, 28 Oct 2005; cuid1217; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Security in Ghana, undated; cuid1218; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Raw Video: Downtown Show, 27 Jan 2006; cuid1219; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - "Ultraviolet", 18 Apr 2006; cuid1220; 8 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Zukerman Forum 2006, 18 Apr 2006; cuid1221; 4 minidvs (Box 74)
  - National Public Policy Forum Debate, 22 Apr 2006; cuid1222; 4 minidvs (Box 74)
  - King Juan Carlos Center, 1 Dec 2005; cuid1223; 2 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Wagner Admissions Video, 11 Apr 2006; cuid1224; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Leo Barsanili and Lehman Lecture, 11 Apr 2006; cuid1225; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 74)
  - Promo "Cribs" PSA, 12 Sep 2002; cuid1226; 1 minidvs (Box 74)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 1, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1227; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Season 3 Islam, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1228; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 5, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1229; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 7 Britain, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1230; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 9 Britain, 20 Oct 2006; cuid1231; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 10 Britain, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1232; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 12 France, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1233; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 14 United States, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1234; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 16 India, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1235; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Entrepreneurship Conference Session 18 Japan, 21 Oct 2006; cuid1236; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008: Preliminary Rounds B-roll, 22 Feb 2008; cuid1237; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008, 22 Feb 2008; cuid1238; 4 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008 Finals, 10 Apr 2008; cuid1239; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008 Finals, 10 Apr 2008; cuid1240; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates 2008 Panel, 22 Feb 2008; cuid1241; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 75)
  - Siemens Competition Program History, 4 Dec 2006; cuid1242; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Siemns Competition Awards Ceremony, 4 Dec 2006; cuid1243; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - September 11: Our University Remembers, 11 Sep 2006; cuid1244; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Robert Rosenblum Symposium, 14 Oct 2006; cuid1245; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Al Gore: Policy Address on Climate Change, 18 Sep 2006; cuid1246; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Spotlights: Ann Morning, Perry Halkitis, 23 Aug 2005; cuid1247; 5 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Highlights Corrections, 10 Dec 2005; cuid1248; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Promo, undated; cuid1249; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs: Ann Morning Rought Segments, undated; cuid1250; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Public Affairs Highlights Promo, 9 Apr 2009; cuid1251; 1 videocassettes (Box 75)
  - President of Cyprus, 18 Sep 2009; cuid1252; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Metro Tech Education Meeting, 17 Jul 2006; cuid1253; 2 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Who Makes Policy on Africa? Raw Footage and Master Tapes, 17 Apr 2006; cuid1254; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Edward Wilson Lecture, 3 Jan 2007; DV; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Edward Wilson Lecture, 3 Jan 2007; cuid1255; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 75)
  - How to Get Into Translation Business, 24 Mar 2007; cuid1256; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - How to Get Into Translation Business, 24 Mar 2007; cuid1257; 2 dvd-r disks (Box 75)
  - Civil Rights Symposium, 28 Oct 2006; cuid1258; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Who's in Charge? Old Media, New Media, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1259; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - SCPS Marketing: Naomi Levine, 30 Apr 2007; cuid1260; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Chat with Financiers: Ajit Jain, 7 May 2007; cuid1261; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Wagner Intersections: Leslie Stahl Discussion, 1 Mar 2007; cuid1262; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Social Entreprenuership in the 21st Century, 1 Mar 2007; cuid1263; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Expanding the Vision: Recovery as a New, undated; cuid1264; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Trade and Africa Culture: Opening Remarks, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1265; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Trade and Africa Culture: The Millenium Village, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1266; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Trade an Africa Culture: African Agriculture, 8 Nov 2006; cuid1267; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Ourspace: DIY Media and the Future of Democracy, 9 Nov 2006; cuid1268; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Bill Drayton Lecture, 13 Oct 2006; cuid1269; 3 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Bill Drayton Lecture, 13 Oct 2006; cuid1270; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - MIAP Speaker Series: How to Find Film and Videos, 22 Sep 2006; cuid1271; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates, 20 Apr 2006; cuid1272; 4 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Zuckerman Debates, 20 Apr 2006; cuid1273; 4 dvd-r disks (Box 75)
  - Raw Stock Footage: Snow in Washington Square Park, 7 Mar 2007; cuid1274; 1 minidvs (Box 75)
  - Hope Not Hate, 8 Sep 2002; cuid1275; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Hip Hop Journalism, 26 Oct 2004; cuid1276; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Grossberg Lecture, undated; cuid1277; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Robert McChesney Lecture, 11 Nov 2004; cuid1278; 2 videocassettes (Box 77)
  - Ultraviolet, undated; cuid1279; 3 minidvs (Box 76, Box 77)
  - Campus Flash: Adutumn Fest, Ticket Central, 1 Sep 2002; cuid1280; 3 minidvs (Box 76, Box 77)
  - Zantee Hou Interview for IRHC, undated; cuid1281; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Presidential Debate, 1 Nov 2004; cuid1282; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Beyond the Sea Segement CF, 1 Sep 2004; cuid1283; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Hayden Talent Show, undated; cuid1284; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Teach In: Who is Next? "North Korea and Beyond", 1 Apr 2003; cuid1285; 5 minidvs (Box 76, Box 77)
  - Lost in Translation: Rough Final Cut PSA, undated; cuid1286; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - NYU TV Coming up Slate 2002, cuid1287; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - New York University Cribs 2003, cuid1288; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - University Stock Footage, undated; cuid1289; 4 minidvs (Box 76, Box 77)
  - Women Who Cook for a Living in New York and Why, 11 Jul 2006; cuid1290; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Diet & Nutrition: Counseling a Dental Office, 8 Sep 2001; cuid1291; 3 minidvs (Box 76)
  - The Relationship of Health Promotion, 25 Oct 2001; cuid1292; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Real Estate, 24 Oct 2001; cuid1293; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Habib Kiote, 5 Oct 2001; cuid1294; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - HIPAA School of Social Work, 24 mar 2003; cuid1295; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Gloria Cahill Interview, 21 Sep 2005; cuid1296; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Max Orestein: Hurricane Katrina Photography, 1 Nov 2005; cuid1297; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Aviva Levine Interview, 26 Sep 2009; cuid1298; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Bronfman Center Katrina Panel, 14 Sep 2005; cuid1299; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Senior Class Council c/o 2006, 3 Nov 2005; cuid1300; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Applefest, undated; cuid1301; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - The Matador movie press kit and interviews, undated; cuid1302; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - The Matador Brosnan Interview, undated; cuid1303; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Presidential Welcome 2004 (NYU class of 2008), cuid1304; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - TVC B-Roll, undated; cuid1305; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - NYU-TV Channel 15 Movie Promos F02/S03, undated; cuid1306; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - "25th Hour" Movie Promo and NYU TV Promo, 15 Sep 2003; cuid1307; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Bobst Interviews and Stand-Ups, 20 Jul 2001; cuid1308; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Bobst Stand-Ups and Exteriors, 20 Jul 2001; cuid1309; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Bobst Steadicam, 20 Jul 2001; cuid1310; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - "War Retold" Photographs of Vietnam by Serene Ford Northington, 8 Apr 2003; cuid1311; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - "War Retold" Photographs of Vietnam by Serene Ford Northington and her Mother, 16 Apr 2003; cuid1312; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Bobst B-Roll, 1 Jan 2002; cuid1313; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Campus Flash: Holiday Stress, 1 Dec 2002; cuid1314; 3 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Coles Writing, Center, and Bobst Archives Footage, 1 Jan 2001; cuid1315; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Lauren Acuna: New Channel 1, 1 Jan 2001; cuid1316; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - APA Artist Talk: Serene Ford Northington, 25 Feb 2003; cuid1317; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - SWANK Motion Pictures Promo, 1 Jan 2002; cuid1318; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - NYU Channel 15 Movie Promo, 1 Nov 2002; cuid1319; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Cooking Series: David Kamp, 6 Oct 2002; cuid1320; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - NYU Journalism: Jimmy Breslin Lecture, 18 Sep 2002; cuid1321; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Tisch School of Arts International Student Film, 28 Oct 2003; cuid1322; 2 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Big Valentine's Fun Day, 1 Feb 2002; cuid1323; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - ABA Dialogue on Freedom Slate, 22 Oct 2002; cuid1324; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Vision Fest 2004, 1 Jan 2004; cuid1325; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Welcome to New York University, undated; cuid1326; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - NYU TV Logo Animations, undated; cuid1327; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Food Series: From Here to There, Food Chains, 19 Oct 2006; cuid1328; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Food Series: "What We Eat" by Marion Nestle, 4 May 2006; cuid1329; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - National Endowment for the Arts NEW 4, 15 Apr 2004; cuid1330; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - ITP Interactive Telecommunications Program, 13 May 2003; cuid1331; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - "Film School" IFC Docu-series Junket and Campus, 23 Aug 2004; cuid1332; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - NYU TV Christmas and Happy Holidays 2001 Promo, 9 Dec 2001; cuid1333; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - FBI Mon. Class Project 3, 1 Jan 2003; cuid1334; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Remarque Lecture: Mark Danner The Politics of the Forever War, 14 Nov 2006; cuid1335; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Stand-up Founder's Memorial, 1 Jul 2005; cuid1336; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Inside NYU: Historic NYU, Campus Tour, 1 Jul 2005; cuid1337; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Deutsches Haus, Ireland House, 27 Jul 2005; cuid1338; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Archives, Stand-ups, and more, 22 Jul 2005; cuid1339; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Inside NYU: Marvin Taylor and the Fales Library, 1 Jul 2005; cuid1340; 1 minidvs (Box 76)
  - Conjunctions 25th Anniversary Reading, 7 Dec 2006; cuid1341; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Tony Judt Lecture: "Disturbing the Peace", 4 Dec 2006; cuid1342; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Fales Food Series: "What's with all these books on food?", 12 Dec 2006; cuid1343; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Translating the World: Engaging Americans in International Journalism, 2 Feb 2007; cuid1344; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - MLK Celebration Week at NYU: A Tribute to Dr. Martin Luther King, 17 Jan 2007; cuid1345; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Moving Archipelago: A Century of Writing Filipino America, 11 Nov 2007; cuid1346; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Entering at One's Own Rish: Dennis Cooper and Transgressive Writing, 1 Mar 2007; cuid1347; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - US Senator Charles E. Schumer (D-NY) at NYU, 21 Feb 2007; cuid1348; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Sharing the Life of Lisa Ellen Goldberg Memorial, 25 Feb 2007; cuid1349; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - My Semina Photography: A Conversation with Dennis Hopper, 12 Feb 2007; cuid1350; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - My Semina Photography: A Conversation with Dennis Hopper, 12 Feb 2007; cuid1351; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 76)
  - Artist's Circles: How do they work and what do they do?, 25 Jan 2007; cuid1352; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - NYU's Media Talk: The Literary Life and the Print Editor's changing role in the world of Web 2.0 with Mr. Carr, 20 Mar 2007; cuid1353; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - NYU Masters Program in Global Health: Moving Beyond Rhetoric and Toward Solutions, 30 Jan 2007; cuid1354; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - NYU Masters Program in Global Health: Public Health, 27 Feb 2007; cuid1355; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Library: Harry Frankfurt, 19 Mar 2007; cuid1356; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Intersections with Lesley Stahl: A Discusssion with Irshad Manji, 5 Mar 2007; cuid1357; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Intersections with Lesley Stahl: A Discusssion with Irshad Manji, 5 Mar 2007; cuid1358; 1 dvd-r disks (Box 76)
  - Courant Masters Orientation, 11 Jan 2007; cuid1359; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Fales lecture B-Roll "Up is Up, But so is Down", 26 Oct 2007; cuid1360; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Fales: Writing New York Talks from Gotham City, 17 Apr 2007; cuid1361; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Leonard N. Stern Schoiol of Business: Ashok Sani, 27 Mar 2007; cuid1362; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - After CBGB: Gender, Sexuality, and the Future of Subculture, 13 Apr 2007; cuid1363; 3 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - MIAP & ITP: A Talk with Archivist & Visual Designer, 23 Mar 2007; cuid1364; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Cooking with Color, 8 Mar 2007; cuid1365; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Greg Albanis - Security Training for Commencement, 22 Mar 2007; cuid1366; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Gallatin Panel: Body Image, 29 Mar 2007; cuid1367; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Casa Italiana, 8 Mar 2007; cuid1368; 2 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Downtown Gallery B-Roll, 6 Feb 2006; cuid1369; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Downtown Galley Grey Art Gallery Tour, 6 Feb 2007; cuid1370; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Downtown Show Art Clips for Grey Art Gallery, 6 Feb 2007; cuid1371; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Scholars and Artists: D.J. Rehka Interview, 27 Aug 2007; cuid1372; 6 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Scholars and Artists: D.J. Rehka Interview, 27 Aug 2007; cuid1373; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Politics & Parnoia Opening and Panels, 31 Mar 2007; cuid1374; 6 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Building a Food Professional Pedigree: New Roads to Knowledge and Success, 14 Jun 2007; cuid1375; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Journeys to Equity in Education: Dr.Wanda, 18 Jul 2007; cuid1376; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Journeys to Equity in Education: Dr. Pedro Noguera, 18 Jul 2007; cuid1377; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Journeys to Equity in Education: Dr. Aretha Ball, 19 Jul 2007; cuid1378; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 76)
  - Stern: Credit Crunch and Subprime Markets, 5 Nov 2007; cuid1379; 2 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - College of Arts and Science Fall 2007, 3 Dec 2007; cuid1380; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - Israel at 60, 9 Dec 2007; cuid1381; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 77)
  - A/P/A YellowFace Interview, 8 Dec 2007; cuid1382; 1 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Thirteen/WNET "Can We Disagree", 1 Jan 2008; cuid1383; 4 minidvs (Box 77)
  - Reynolds Social Entrepreneurship in the 21st Century, 30 Jan 2008; cuid1384; 1 minidvs (Box 77)